

QUALITY ASSURANCE (QA)
ANALYST

#### **Details**

Meerkoetstraat, Capelle aan den IJssel, 2903EP, Netherlands +31621321121 danielboone1990@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Dutch

DATE OF BIRTH

17-11-1990

### Links

LinkedIn

#### **Skills**

MS SOL

Cypress.io

Visual Studio 2017 Enterprise

Git

C# .NET

Oracle

MS Team Foundation Server

Gherkin

#### Languages

Thai

Dutch

English

#### **Profile**

Detailed-oriented, driven Quality Assurance Analyst with extensive experience in manual testing as test automation. Deep understanding of Agile work processes and experience working with Scrum methodologies. Skilled in various test automation tools e.g. Cypress, Specflow, Gherkin and Selenium.

## **Employment History**

#### Quality Assurance Analyst, DSW Zorgverzekeraar, Schiedam

NOVEMBER 2018

- Implement and monitor test scripts to assess functionality, reliability, performance, and quality of the service or product
- Find, record, track bugs, and perform thorough documentation
- Mentor and lead team on test automation
- Identify resource requirements, effectively plan, define test strategy, provide quality assurance estimate, and provide test management and test reporting throughout the testing cycle
- Analyze and identify bugs in application source code and collaborate closely with developers to solve the problems

## Sales Consultant, Go Beyond Asia, Chiang Mai

JULY 2017 - AUGUST 2018

- Drive sales to achieve targets
- Develop new selling strategies to grow revenue
- Plan and evaluate sales and marketing data
- Ensure qualitative after-sales services
- Create customers' MS SQL database and update sales data
- Write MS SQL queries to generate sales reports in MS Excel
- Assist and support account receivables team

### Data Analyst Intern, Plymovent Manufacturing Thailand, Lamphun

JANUARY 2017 - JULY 2017

- Assist with implementation of SAP enterprise resource system
- Developing and executing processes for monitoring, maintaining, improving and restoring quality in Oracle database
- Developed macro's in MS excel to discover data flaws
- Assignment on master data management

#### Webmaster intern, Greenwood Travel, Bangkok

JULY 2015 - FEBRUARY 2016

- Setup WordPress blogging website for advertisement purposes
- Create monthly magazine with WIX.com
- Automated monthly mailing to subscribers
- Maintain, update website contents and address technical issues

### **Education**

#### Bachelor, University of Applied Sciences, Rotterdam

JULY 2014 - JULY 2017

Business Administration with an exchange program at ICO NIDA, Bangkok in 2016 as well 2 international internships in Bangkok and Lamphun.

### Courses

Practitioner in Agile Quality, iSQI GmbH

JANUARY 2020

## Hobbies

Socializing with friends
Explore new technologies/tools
Travelling
Stock market

# TMap© Suite Test Engineer, EXIN

APRIL 2019

# IELTS, Cambridge English Language Assessment

JULY 2020 - JULY 2020

# References

Lennart Otten from DSW Zorgverzekeraar

Lennartotten@live.nl

Quoc Nguyen from DSW Zorgverzekeraar

Quoc.nguyen@vanquoc.com